<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Powercore&#39;s Place in Space</title>
    <link>https://powercore2000.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Powercore&#39;s Place in Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://powercore2000.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My biggest problem with the Unity Asset Store</title>
      <link>https://powercore2000.github.io/blogs/my-biggest-problem-with-the-unity-asset-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://powercore2000.github.io/blogs/my-biggest-problem-with-the-unity-asset-store/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve bought hundreds of products off the Unity Asset Store in my time.
While my list of shame may not be the longest, among my fellow unity developers, it&amp;rsquo;s still sitting around 500 assets at the time of writing this post. And I can confidently say I don&amp;rsquo;t regret almost any of my asset purchases up to this point. It was my love for purchasing assets and imagining what I could make with them that inspired me to make my Cyberspace Crusade program that powers my YouTube channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on the GPT to Unity Project</title>
      <link>https://powercore2000.github.io/blogs/update-on-gpt-to-unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 05:51:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://powercore2000.github.io/blogs/update-on-gpt-to-unity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello, hello!
Almost 3 months ago I announced my plans to make a tool named GPT to Unity, which was meant to provide access to OpenAi&amp;rsquo;s back-end system inside of the Unity Engine. At the time there were no other tools on the asset store providing that utility, and I found it would have been a fun project to test my web development skills by using ASP.Net Core. Since that announcement, a number of personal delays dramatically slowed development, and other solutions have been posted on the Unity Asset Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>https://powercore2000.github.io/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://powercore2000.github.io/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
